//This javascript file is to hold an array to contain each question and answers
var questions = [
    {
        "question": "Which of these scare you the most?",
        "answers": ["spiders", "heights", "commitment", "change"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these colors do you prefer?",
        "answers": ["green", "blue", "red", "yellow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "If you could only have one of these pets, what kind of pet would it be?",
        "answers": ["dog", "cat", "bird", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these books do you prefer?",
        "answers": ["Brief History of Time", "Of Mice and Men", "Harry Potter", "I don't read books"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these movies do you prefer?",
        "answers": ["Birdman", "Inglourious Basterds", "The Goonies", "I don't watch movies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which artist do you prefer?",
        "answers": ["Explosions in the Sky", "Kendrick Lamar", "The Beatles", "I don't like music"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What season do you prefer?",
        "answers": ["Winter", "Spring", "Summer", "Autumn"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these places would you rather take a vacation to?",
        "answers": ["Tokyo", "Bruges", "Paris", "Hawaii"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your ideal date?",
        "answers": ["Cuddle with a movie", "Look at the stars", "Go on a hike", "Go ski/snowboard"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What attribute do you respect the most?",
        "answers": ["kindness", "respect", "humor", "honesty"]
    }
]

// module.exports = questions;